theyallhateus.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | TheyAllHateUs

We recognize the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. Unless you directly give us consent to do otherwise, ‘They All Hate Us’ will only collect and use your personal information as set out below. This Privacy Policy is intended to represent industry best practice and comply fully with the Privacy Act 1988.

**What information do we collect?**

We may collect the following information from you:

  * your name and contact details
  * some personal details
  * other information that you will supply to us

**Why we collect the information?**

Our purpose in collecting information about you is to provide you with a better website experience with content that is relevant to your interests. In seeking to give you the most worthwhile experience of our website possible, we may notify you of shop events and special offers that may be of interest to you. The information we collect through http://www.theyallhateus.com helps us better understand the products and services most helpful to you.

**Where we collect the information from?**

We collect the following information that you may be unaware of:

  * the name of the domain from which you access the internet
  * the date and time you access our site
  * the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site

**Does ‘They All Hate Us’ share my information with third parties?**

Personal information collected online will only be disclosed to us. http://www.theyallhateus.com does not share, sell or trade your personal information gathered online, such as email addresses or postal addresses.

**How can I review my choices about receiving promotional communication?**

‘They All Hate Us’ only wants to communicate with you if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information from us or if you do not want your information used to enhance your shopping experience, please let us know by sending us an email to tashandelle@theyallhateus.com with the word ‘unsubscribe’ in the subject field.

Any information that we no longer require is destroyed securely. An exception to this may be retention of the information for data analysis. However, if this occurs then the information will be retained in a form that does not allow you to be identified from that information.

**How can I access my personal information?**

You may review, change or delete personal information related to your use of our online site. To review your information, simply send us an email to tashandelle@theyallhateus.com requesting access to the information we hold about you.
